What's this?
Onizaki?
Anyway, just watch.
One day in August.
In northern Saitama Prefecture...
JR Kodama Station.
And showing up, none the wiser,
is a lone comedian.
It's Takano.
Who enjoys this?!
His versatile, foul-mouthed retorts have
been getting him attention in the industry.
Takano, of Kishi-Takano.
This idiot comedian...
...is our target today.
What's with this narration? That's awful.
What's your name?
Takano...
He said, "Get in the car."
Me?
Who gets in just from "Get in that car"?!
Fine, fine, I get it.
That car? Yeah.
You're getting in?
And just like that, the Takano pickup was
a success.
I don't get any of this.
And so,
the Comedian Uber Eats...
...began its delivery run.
Wait, what's happening?
I have no idea where they're taking me.
Comedians are the easiest people to
kidnap.
Just tell them "Please get in," and they
have to do it.
Told to get in, they get in.
Most comedians have been conditioned
into this Pavlovian response.
Comedian instinct.
Seriously, what's going on?
This is terrifying.
The driver is... an Oni.
The destination is Hell, located deep in
the deserted mountains.
What the hell is this?
Are we here?
And then...
Oh god, I hate this.
Stop being so reckless! Seriously! It's
scary. This is the worst. I hate it.
I wasn't told anything about this!
This is scary.
Full of suspicion, Takano enters the
ruins. What? Seriously?
Oh god, it's so scary...
Huh? What?
Don't be reckless!
Is this coming off?
No, seriously, stop.
Jeez.
What are you doing? Oh, this is bad.
Pulling it out? You're pulling it out?
He's pulling it out.
Wait, he's already got it out! This can't
be for TV!
His dick is out.
Wait, stop.
What is this?
What?
A TV show.
A special.
Broadcast TV?
Broadcast TV.
His d*ck's out.
Yep, it's out.
Can you show d*cks on TV?
No! But it's right there!
Oh, it must be pixelated.
It must be.
Whoa, I saw it!
Huh?
You can't show a dick on broadcast TV, but
some random guy can just whip his out in public.
And then people on set say...
Harassment.
It's...
...unbelievable! I'm a professional!
You're a director too, you should know!
I've never made a show with dicks in it!
I never have!
-What's this show? -Onizaki's. I directed
it. A demon puts comedians through hell. Anything goes if it's funny. -But that was a dick! Can you air that?!
Just watch it for now, okay? Then tell me
what you think.
Okay.
This is on TV? Seriously?
His junk is out.
This is nuts.
W-What...
is that?
A diaper?
What the hell? This is insane.
This... Ugh.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. For real?
This is so crude.
This idea is 20 years old.
So Onizaki.
Oh, this is bad.
His d*ck was out. What's this text?
What is this?
This is seriously messed up.
Here.
This is so disgusting.
Wait, what kind of "hell" is this?
Help me.
Takano's Confinement Escape He-
-ll. And with that,
Takano's life in just a diaper begins.
Never heard of a "diaper-only life."
This?
Huh?
This time, your personal hell is the
'Escape from Captivity Hell'.
Rule #1: To escape, you must collect 1
million yen from people on the outside. One million?!
Whoever brings you money must come alone.
If they're not alone, it won't count.
Right.
Takano's personal hell:
He's trapped in these remote ruins on the
border of Gunma and Saitama.
Until he collects 1 million yen,
he can't return to the outside world.
"The outside world"...? His only contact
is a smartphone.
However, you can only talk for 15 minutes
each hour.
You can't tell anyone you call that this
is for a TV show. If they find out, the call is void.
This is Wednesday Downtown.
I'm sure of it.
We're not that big of a show.
Wait, this is just hell, isn't it?
What the hell? Diapers?
Oh, this is my phone.
Oh, it's in here.
My phone. How do I get this out?
So I can't take it out? Oh, there it is.
Oh, it moves!
Once every 15 minutes?
The smartphone, which is the key to your
escape,
is inside the Oni Box. (What's an Oni
Box?!) To make a call, you have to put your arm inside.
the oni's mouth snaps shut,
a harsh system where you must make the
call while in excruciating pain.
Is this really necessary?
Ow, ow, ow! It hurts!
No way.
It hurts!
Do we need this?
This whole painful system.
Oh, man. That's gotta be awful.
(laughs)
What is this situation?
Right.
I need to
get someone.
I have to make a call.
Calling Miyazawa of Zigzag Ziggy.
Can he do it in that state?
What a tiny sound.
The stress must be insane.
Hello? It's me.
Hey, what's up? Yeah, sorry, but...
Could you bring me some money?
What?
I need you to bring me some money. Whoa,
whoa, hold on.
Right, right. Yes.
Excuse me. / Yes? / I was hoping you could
lend me some money.
Money? Right.
How much?
One...
...million yen, maybe?
One million?
Wh-what for?
Of course you'd ask that.
Well...
I need it.
I have a situation I can't talk about.
Come on, you have to tell me the reason.
Just lend it to me.
This is tough.
Well... I don't have any money to lend you
right now.
Shit!
Why the English? Sorry, I'm in a hurry.
See, I have a job coming up... as a
pro-wrestling ring announcer.
Don't "what" me. It's my call time.
Sorry. What? Okay, I get it.
Ask me later.
Excuse me, I'm leaving.
Sorry, I have to go.
Okay, okay.
Whoa!
A ring announcer job for pro wrestling?
That's great! Oh.
What to do...
Of course I'm going to ask why! We've been
through so much together.
Trust me and lend it!
It's hot!
So many factors...
I'll call Tomoshige (MOGURAIDER).
Hello? Yes.
Hello? Sorry.
Sorry, uh...
Yes?
I need a loan.
Money? Uh, sorry.
- Huh? How much?
- A million, if you can? Sorry.
What...
...a way to ask!
Ah...
- What's wrong?
- So I can? Really?
- What will you use it for?
- Sorry... I'll accept it.
Incredible...
I'll explain, but I need you to bring it
over.
T-today?
Yes, today.
Look, I'm on a gig right now. I'm in
Fukushima.
Fukushima... It's far.
So...
I just finished and am heading back.
It'll take 3 hours... maybe 4 or 5.
Five hours...
But...
I still need you to bring it.
Huh?
The big one?
It's a once-in-a-lifetime favor.
It's over...
It's not cutting...
Hell. Ouch.
Huh? This is rough. Fukushima?
Fukushima? What island?
Cut it out.
I hate this heat.
Toilet? / Huh?
For real?
You're kidding me.
This isn't TV.
Whoa. This is nuts.
That was scary. So that's what the diapers
were for.
That's hilarious.
Yeah, it's funny, but I was a bit put off.
It's a bit much.
Nah, I still think it's hilarious.
So no bathroom breaks for him?
They made him wear a diaper. That's what's
too much.
Good work today.
Hey.
Good work. / Oh.
Maybe on a variety show 20 years ago, but
not now.
A prank like this must turn off young
people like you, right?
It doesn't bother me. / Huh?
The more you unreasonably push Takano-san,
the funnier he gets.
I see. So you're that kind of fan,
Momokawa?
That type.
Yes.
Shinku Jeshka.
The fan-turned-staffer type?
Yeah.
I went to comedy shows and wanted to work
with them.
A fan of Takano? No, not a fan.
I like comedy, but I'm not a fan.
Don't be so quick to deny it.
Well, let's just watch this to the end.
And...
...an additional rule.
The Oni can't bring the million all at
once.
It's boring if it's not split up.
The Oni talks?
If the Oni brings it all at once...
...Huh?
Hell Darts.
You throw them.
Be careful.
Why?!
Fair enough.
Why is it 'Hell Darts'
if I get it in one go?
I'm in hell... and if I get it in one go,
they call it 'Hell Darts.'
He's right. They strip you naked,
Then...
throw you in filth,
and get your hands caught.
Darts of Hell. So convincing.
It's hot.
Cicadas.
Oh, here he comes, here he comes.
Couldn't you at least "beep"?
Ow! What was that? It's my senior,
Yasuhara Karasu, with his petty pranks.
Yasuhara-san.
You gotta show yourself now!
He started calling down his list of people
to hit up for cash.
Huh? How much? Well, um...
How much can you spot me?
Uhh...
Just 25,000 yen?
Yeah.
You gonna pay me back?
How much? Well, I was thinking...
Like, 100,000? Or 200,000?
No, no, no. Sorry, sorry. Seriously.
I'm broke too, man. But please, help me.
Awesome! But he only found comics who
could lend 10-20,000 yen.
The round ended with him nowhere near his
goal.
It's so hot. I get so worked up.
Worked up?
I'm sweating buckets.
I'm fine here, but it gets so hot on the
phone.
Who to call... Right. Can't be anyone
broke.
This feels awful...
As expected, he launches into his usual
complaints.
(sighs)
But the only response...
...is the piercing cry...
...of cicadas.
And then...
Two and a half hours in.
Time for the third phone call.
What will he do?
Here it comes.
It should be ringing. Yeah.
Minamikawa.
That came in so quietly.
Hello? Hey there.
- What's up? - Hello? What are you up to
today? - Nothing planned for later, but...
I'm in Atsugi right now, though.
Oh, right.
On my way back.
Um, there was a...
death in the family.
So I went home...
and I ended up spending all my money.
So I was hoping...
you could lend me money for a payment.
Oh. How much?
100,000...
Whoa...
Ah...
Okay... / He's asking for more.
Could I maybe get 300,000?
A huge help.
"300k for what? For who?"
"Right... for my grandma."
Your grandma? 300k for your grandma?
Didn't your grandma just pass away?
Yes.
"What do you mean?" "We're short on
funds." "Think! Just tell me what for!"
I'll lend it. Just tell me what for.
"It's for..." "This is your chance!"
"...the funeral flowers."
Not wanting to miss his chance, Takano...
...abruptly kills off his grandma
and doubles down on his funeral scam.
Whoa, whoa. A funeral scam.
"Thank you so much." "Seriously?"
He managed to get 300,000 yen from
Minamikawa. Amazing, Namikawa-san. And there's more.
Also... for cigarettes, water, a bento...
if there's a convenience store, could you buy...
...some for me?
How shameless.
What's with you?
Huh?
Of course he's mad.
What... What the hell?
What the hell? What is that? I mean...
It's for the wake.
Cigarettes? -Cigarettes and a bento.
Who are they for? You? -For my grandma.
Your g-grandma?
Okay, got it.
Right. I'm a bit tied up right now.
It's a bit of a pain. You'll come? Okay.
So, um...
When you get to Tanshō Station,
give me another call.
That's the plan.
And so,
he managed to guide them to the location.
Next. - Hey, Takano here. - Hi. Got a
minute?
Takano... So, uh...
with, like, a gravure model...
There's this get-together,
They asked for people, so I thought of
you. - You change your tune? Huh?
What time?
- Yes?
- Well, um...
Well, I'm already going.
Really?
- Yeah.
- Food? - No, we're supposed to buy a gift
and all chip in. - What kind of party is that?
Okay. So can I just give you money for my
share?
- Yeah, that's fine. - So you'll buy it? -
I'll take care of it.
Got it. Right, right.
- I'll get it. - Got it, okay. - So...
Okay, got it.
Can you lend me the cash?
Wait, 20k? 200k? I'll need 200,000.
200,000?!
What are you buying?
I'll manage with 100k.
We're splitting it?
We'll split it.
And so, he succeeded in getting the two of
them to come out.
And now, we wait again.
So that's 400k now.
So dirty.
Aaaah...
Jeez...
Visually, it's hilarious.
It's getting ridiculous.
The wide shot is probably the best angle.
As the sun began to set,
Takano grew stressed by the poor
conditions.
There's a futon.
What do I do with this?
Can I use this to pull something over?
He found a pile of trash
left in a corner of the ruins.
Ugh.
Oh.
Ah! I want that futon!
You really do want a futon. And this
bucket... I guess it'll work.
It's like a chair.
Whoa.
Ahh. Oh.
So much more comfortable.
What are we even watching? In this
hellscape, Takano has regained a shred of his humanity.
I feel like some of my stress has
disappeared.
What?
This
A picture! Yeah!
Wow.
Alright!
Oh.
Getting comfy, bit by bit.
Here he comes.
He's here! Whoa, he's huge. He's down.
Come on, notice him!
The guy on the phone is desperate. He's
disappeared. That's why it's so quiet.
He's right behind you!
Hey! Wait, no, that's not... Oh, it is!
I had no clue... At least make a sound!
Ouch. You looked pretty satisfied. How many times do I have to do this "ouch" routine?
Ah, what a total waste. My arm hurts...
One minute.
Aida from Sanshiro.
Hello? It's Takano.
Hey there. Aida-san, what are you up to
today?
I'm in Asahikawa right now.
Asahikawa... in Hokkaido. Sorry, I'm gonna
hang up for a sec.
Wait, what? -Bye.
Okay, bye.
So, what are you up to today?
Today? I'm in Hokkaido.
Hokkaido?
Yeah, for a gig. -Okay. -A gig. What are
you doing? Not everyone here. See?
Where's the gig? Asahikawa, right?
Asahikawa... Oh.
Alright, my bad.
Hokkaido, seriously?
What's even in Hokkaido?
Oh, come on.
Seriously, this past hour was a bust.
A complete waste of time.
I feel like I could make some shoes with
this.
Ah.
Hey! It's all over your clothes!
And...
With tools he found in the garbage pile,
The diaper comedian resumes his 'dignity
restoration'.
This is all for my dignity. Yes.
That was close.
I was about to lose it.
Oh.
What'd he grab?
Alright.
Yes! So happy. What are these? Socks!
So happy!
Whoa, so much better. I get it now. So
comfy.
Socks are way comfier than barefoot. I
totally disagree.
Opposite.
Se—
—riously? What an expression.
I've never done this, I can't move.
That first step...
Scary.
Huh?
This is the worst.
No toilet, either?
Seriously...?
Oh, it's coming.
Are you really?
It's happening. This is nuts.
This is nuts. What's the best position?
Should I sit? We're about to see something
wild.
Don't call this the highlight. Oh...
I'm gonna pee.
Seriously?
Ahhh, it's coming...
Oh, it's coming.
Coming out.
You're doing it standing up.
Ah.
Oh. It's there. Crap.
It is.
Oh.
It's out...
It's out. Oh no, I did it. I have a really
bad feeling.
Whoa, it's a bat.
Whoa, seriously, no way. I can't handle
this.
I can't calm down at all.
After seeing a bat.
And there are so many. I saw one.
What now?
Oh, here it comes. Oh, this is fine. If
it's coming from that way, it's allowed.
They're coming down.
They really...
...thought out these rules.
What, a mountain path? This is way too
far! And it's terrifying!
That's correct.
For ¥300,000.
There's a bridge.
After you cross it,
go down the stairs,
Down the stairs?
Yes, you'll find a building.
So scary.
It's there. So scary.
No, this is just too scary.
What the heck?
Hey! Don't mess with me.
Namikawa-san?
Thank god.
You came, Namikawa-san! Please, come in.
What are you doing here? Help me!
This is absolutely terrifying.
He must be so happy.
"Ah, I see." "Don't 'I see' me!"
First off, thank you for coming.
Catches on quick.
Thanks for making the long trip.
It was so far. - Thanks again. They just
gave me the address... Wait, is that guy in a diaper?
So this isn't *Wed Downtown*?
Would they go this far?
Broadcast TV? - Sharp. / So it's not *Wed
Downtown*?
So we're in diaper territory now. /
Meaning, no bathroom breaks.
I've got nothing.
Did you bring any money?
- Yeah, I did. / - Sorry, that was a weird
question.
- I brought 300k, just in case. / -
300,000?!
Well, for drinks and stuff... / I figured
for you... um...
Lunch, drinks, and cigarettes, right?
You're a great senpai. -Cigarettes?
-Anything's fine.
No lighter.
Here.
Really?
Oh, for me?
Huh? Are you mad?
Just now. You got annoyed, right?
No, wait. I drove for 2 hours, speeding
here...
...to get annoyed at my senpai now?
It wasn't like that.
I've just been sitting here.
Oh.
Oh, tea. Thanks.
You haven't had any?
It's okay, go ahead.
Where'd you find this? It's amazing.
It's so good.
Mmm.
You guys are the best. Seriously.
Hey, mine!
I was genuinely worried about you.
I'm so glad you're okay.
Okay... Whoa! That's awesome.
Thank you. It worked.
That's great.
Oh, change! Thank you. Thank you so much.
I'll take...
...this. Huh?
Takano. Huh? What?
Takano.
What? Good morning. / - Good morning.
Lied?
Sorry.
There's no way we'd have a mixer here. /
It's not that I tricked you, exactly.
You're the worst.
No, no.
(Tch)
I should've known. This is the absolute
worst. It can't get any worse.
It's a 2 or 3 hour trip home.
What kind of mixer is this?! A simple
'sorry' isn't enough.
1,000 yen.
Whoa.
For real? I don't get it yet.
Won 100,000 yen. Totaling 400,000...
You came here all ready to get lucky,
bringing a ton of condoms.
Cond...
That's not happening here. I'm really
sorry.
Could you put that down? / I'm Dousucchi.
Oh.
A cigarette?
Thank you.
Thanks.
I'm sorry.
Whoa.
It's huge.
¥400k for the two of us. That's huge.
This is where we're at.
Two hours have passed since Shinichi got
home.
And his phone negotiations have failed.
Thanks anyway.
What even is this segment?
This is crazy, right? Yeah.
This is nuts, seriously. It really is.
And then...
Huh? What's this over here?
Huh? "Ko"...
What the heck?
Whoa, what's this? He's starting to look
like he actually lives here.
Who? What? Who? "Ko"? "Taiko"?
What is this?
What is this? Naiko? Thanks. This is
terrifying.
Come in.
Is this really okay? / Yeah, come on in. /
Taiko, thank you.
Appearing is a junior comedian from Linda
Color∞, who scrapes by working part-time.
Taiko.
Did you bring money? / I did.
Thanks, thanks, thanks!
I brought all the cash I had.
50,000? / No, 180,000.
You're lending me 180,000?
Well, you said you needed help.
You're so kind. Um...
To help the struggling Takano, Taiko
scraped together what little money he had.
So much cash.
Thank you.
Thanks. That makes 15,000 yen. Wow.
Really, thanks.
Wow, this helps more than I expected.
Really.
Pants.
And finally...
(Narrator) He also gets the underwear
Takano was wearing. - Huh? - That is weird.
- That's crazy!
- I feel less like a prisoner.
- You gave him your underwear?
- That's a surprising amount.
That 180,000 yen...
I'm so grateful.
He was thinking about his junior,
who came to his aid in a pinch.
So scary. What is this? Who else is there?
Takano? Takano?
What is this? Seriously, what is this?
Tomoshige, who was supposed to be in Fukushima that day...
...traveled 6 hours to get to Takano.
I need... to borrow some money.
No, seriously... I like you, Takano,
and I respect you, but what is this?
You have to explain.
This is terrifying. I need a loan...
...or I can't get out.
And so...
500,000 yen? Are you sure?
Yeah, it's fine.
I'm so sorry. 500,000 yen? Thank you so
much.
This is money for my wife and kid.
This is from our family savings.
Please.
I'm sorry. I will. I promise.
Okay? Thank you.
-Good luck.
This should be enough to get out.
Right.
So, did it work?
50.
Oh, so it worked? Wait,
Amazing.
Whoa. What's this?
Huh?
It's here.
A key. Hmm. Where's the key?
Here it is.
Ah, I can get out.
I can get out! We're out! Whoa!
I made it out! Incredible!
That was scary.
That was close.
What'd you think?
See it all. It's hilarious.
It's hilarious. Right? It really is.
I've never seen footage like that.
Never seen someone pee in a diaper. Right?
Rare footage.
And the 'Dignity Restore.'
I've never heard that phrase before.
'Dignity Restore.'
But you could never air that on TV, right?
I'm amazed they got the OK to air this.
We didn't.
What?
The network shot us down.
On this.
-What do you mean we can't air it? -It's
not up for debate. We can't broadcast that.
What's wrong with it?
The problem is that you, a producer,
think that's okay to air.
-But we already shot it! What do I tell
their agencies? -You're the one who ignored our request and filmed that, Onigoe!
What we asked for...
...was a heartwarming prank show.
They were asked for a "heartwarming prank
show" and made *that*? No wonder it was rejected.
Please!
What?
I need a favor.
Through editing,
turn this footage into something
heartwarming.
What?
The footage is too absurd. There's no
reason for Takano to seem positive.
When Takano gets jailed, he suddenly
starts resisting. It's weird. I'm thinking of changing the on-screen text there. Seriously.
Let's do it!
Oh man, this is gonna be hard.
Okay, let's fix it like this.
Music Station-style.
Music Station. Can you do it?
This is serious, Koshi-san. Huh?
If this doesn't air, the company will go
under.
Will this be moving?
I'll be moved.
- You won't. - What?
Thanks for watching 'Tears from a Devilish
Prank'.
So, how was it? Pretty fun, right?
Amazing, huh?
Fun, right? And this is just the start for
us.
We'll be huge.
They told us to make it heartwarming.
That's what they said.
Like I could do that! How would that even
work?
To see the rest of 'Tears from the Demon
Prank,' sign up for DMM TV.
For first-time subscribers to DMM TV,
you get a 30-day free trial. So if you're
interested, please sign up!